[{"question":"99-33=","type":"-","one":99,"two":33,"correctNum":0,"totalNum":0,"result1":"33","result2":"","correct":false},{"question":"35-18=","type":"-","one":35,"two":18,"correctNum":0,"totalNum":1,"result1":"13","result2":"","correct":false},{"question":"89+66=","type":"+","one":89,"two":66,"correctNum":0,"totalNum":2,"result1":"155","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"87-75=","type":"-","one":87,"two":75,"correctNum":1,"totalNum":3,"result1":"12","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"75-39=","type":"-","one":75,"two":39,"correctNum":2,"totalNum":4,"result1":"36","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"59-13=","type":"-","one":59,"two":13,"correctNum":3,"totalNum":5,"result1":"46","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"77-13=","type":"-","one":77,"two":13,"correctNum":4,"totalNum":6,"result1":"94","result2":"","correct":false},{"question":"78-12=","type":"-","one":78,"two":12,"correctNum":4,"totalNum":7,"result1":"96","result2":"","correct":false},{"question":"23-15=","type":"-","one":23,"two":15,"correctNum":4,"totalNum":8,"result1":"8","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"98-18=","type":"-","one":98,"two":18,"correctNum":5,"totalNum":9,"result1":"80","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"81-53=","type":"-","one":81,"two":53,"correctNum":6,"totalNum":10,"result1":"18","result2":"","correct":false},{"question":"94-83=","type":"-","one":94,"two":83,"correctNum":6,"totalNum":11,"result1":"11","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"67-25=","type":"-","one":67,"two":25,"correctNum":7,"totalNum":12,"result1":"42","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"96-53=","type":"-","one":96,"two":53,"correctNum":8,"totalNum":13,"result1":"43","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"62-55=","type":"-","one":62,"two":55,"correctNum":9,"totalNum":14,"result1":"7","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"81-14=","type":"-","one":81,"two":14,"correctNum":10,"totalNum":15,"result1":"67","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"52-29=","type":"-","one":52,"two":29,"correctNum":11,"totalNum":16,"result1":"23","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"13+11=","type":"+","one":13,"two":11,"correctNum":12,"totalNum":17,"result1":"24","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"95-43=","type":"-","one":95,"two":43,"correctNum":13,"totalNum":18,"result1":"52","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"50-48=","type":"-","one":50,"two":48,"correctNum":14,"totalNum":19,"result1":"2","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"93-51=","type":"-","one":93,"two":51,"correctNum":15,"totalNum":20,"result1":"42","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"14+21=","type":"+","one":14,"two":21,"correctNum":16,"totalNum":21,"result1":"35","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"26-15=","type":"-","one":26,"two":15,"correctNum":17,"totalNum":22,"result1":"11","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"78-13=","type":"-","one":78,"two":13,"correctNum":18,"totalNum":23,"result1":"65","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"36-15=","type":"-","one":36,"two":15,"correctNum":19,"totalNum":24,"result1":"21","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"83-16=","type":"-","one":83,"two":16,"correctNum":20,"totalNum":25,"result1":"67","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"91-54=","type":"-","one":91,"two":54,"correctNum":21,"totalNum":26,"result1":"37","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"88-46=","type":"-","one":88,"two":46,"correctNum":22,"totalNum":27,"result1":"42","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"100-14=","type":"-","one":100,"two":14,"correctNum":23,"totalNum":28,"result1":"86","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"61+14=","type":"+","one":61,"two":14,"correctNum":24,"totalNum":29,"result1":"75","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"87-17=","type":"-","one":87,"two":17,"correctNum":25,"totalNum":30,"result1":"70","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"61-13=","type":"-","one":61,"two":13,"correctNum":26,"totalNum":31,"result1":"48","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"95-72=","type":"-","one":95,"two":72,"correctNum":27,"totalNum":32,"result1":"23","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"90-89=","type":"-","one":90,"two":89,"correctNum":28,"totalNum":33,"result1":"1","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"55-19=","type":"-","one":55,"two":19,"correctNum":29,"totalNum":34,"result1":"46","result2":"","correct":false},{"question":"100-37=","type":"-","one":100,"two":37,"correctNum":29,"totalNum":35,"result1":"63","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"99-57=","type":"-","one":99,"two":57,"correctNum":30,"totalNum":36,"result1":"45","result2":"","correct":false},{"question":"74-29=","type":"-","one":74,"two":29,"correctNum":30,"totalNum":37,"result1":"15","result2":"","correct":false},{"question":"68-52=","type":"-","one":68,"two":52,"correctNum":30,"totalNum":38,"result1":"16","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"39-14=","type":"-","one":39,"two":14,"correctNum":31,"totalNum":39,"result1":"25","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"88-58=","type":"-","one":88,"two":58,"correctNum":32,"totalNum":40,"result1":"30","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"36-19=","type":"-","one":36,"two":19,"correctNum":33,"totalNum":41,"result1":"17","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"60-51=","type":"-","one":60,"two":51,"correctNum":34,"totalNum":42,"result1":"9","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"32+76=","type":"+","one":32,"two":76,"correctNum":35,"totalNum":43,"result1":"108","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"73-31=","type":"-","one":73,"two":31,"correctNum":36,"totalNum":44,"result1":"42","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"92-13=","type":"-","one":92,"two":13,"correctNum":37,"totalNum":45,"result1":"79","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"74-16=","type":"-","one":74,"two":16,"correctNum":38,"totalNum":46,"result1":"58","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"82-43=","type":"-","one":82,"two":43,"correctNum":39,"totalNum":47,"result1":"39","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"100-13=","type":"-","one":100,"two":13,"correctNum":40,"totalNum":48,"result1":"87","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"55-21=","type":"-","one":55,"two":21,"correctNum":41,"totalNum":49,"result1":"34","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"100-46=","type":"-","one":100,"two":46,"correctNum":42,"totalNum":50,"result1":"54","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"43-11=","type":"-","one":43,"two":11,"correctNum":43,"totalNum":51,"result1":"32","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"27-14=","type":"-","one":27,"two":14,"correctNum":44,"totalNum":52,"result1":"13","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"75-28=","type":"-","one":75,"two":28,"correctNum":45,"totalNum":53,"result1":"47","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"85-10=","type":"-","one":85,"two":10,"correctNum":46,"totalNum":54,"result1":"75","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"67-11=","type":"-","one":67,"two":11,"correctNum":47,"totalNum":55,"result1":"56","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"89-86=","type":"-","one":89,"two":86,"correctNum":48,"totalNum":56,"result1":"3","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"93-63=","type":"-","one":93,"two":63,"correctNum":49,"totalNum":57,"result1":"30","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"46+19=","type":"+","one":46,"two":19,"correctNum":50,"totalNum":58,"result1":"65","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"69+10=","type":"+","one":69,"two":10,"correctNum":51,"totalNum":59,"result1":"79","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"39-19=","type":"-","one":39,"two":19,"correctNum":52,"totalNum":60,"result1":"29","result2":"","correct":false},{"question":"71-63=","type":"-","one":71,"two":63,"correctNum":52,"totalNum":61,"result1":"8","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"77+43=","type":"+","one":77,"two":43,"correctNum":53,"totalNum":62,"result1":"120","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"77-73=","type":"-","one":77,"two":73,"correctNum":54,"totalNum":63,"result1":"4","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"76-54=","type":"-","one":76,"two":54,"correctNum":55,"totalNum":64,"result1":"22","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"65-15=","type":"-","one":65,"two":15,"correctNum":56,"totalNum":65,"result1":"50","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"65-18=","type":"-","one":65,"two":18,"correctNum":57,"totalNum":66,"result1":"47","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"59-58=","type":"-","one":59,"two":58,"correctNum":58,"totalNum":67,"result1":"1","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"54-19=","type":"-","one":54,"two":19,"correctNum":59,"totalNum":68,"result1":"35","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"56-28=","type":"-","one":56,"two":28,"correctNum":60,"totalNum":69,"result1":"28","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"94-11=","type":"-","one":94,"two":11,"correctNum":61,"totalNum":70,"result1":"83","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"15+79=","type":"+","one":15,"two":79,"correctNum":62,"totalNum":71,"result1":"94","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"41-18=","type":"-","one":41,"two":18,"correctNum":63,"totalNum":72,"result1":"23","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"77-32=","type":"-","one":77,"two":32,"correctNum":64,"totalNum":73,"result1":"45","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"70-55=","type":"-","one":70,"two":55,"correctNum":65,"totalNum":74,"result1":"15","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"49-29=","type":"-","one":49,"two":29,"correctNum":66,"totalNum":75,"result1":"20","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"93+18=","type":"+","one":93,"two":18,"correctNum":67,"totalNum":76,"result1":"111","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"75-25=","type":"-","one":75,"two":25,"correctNum":68,"totalNum":77,"result1":"50","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"59+12=","type":"+","one":59,"two":12,"correctNum":69,"totalNum":78,"result1":"71","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"78-17=","type":"-","one":78,"two":17,"correctNum":70,"totalNum":79,"result1":"61","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"98-63=","type":"-","one":98,"two":63,"correctNum":71,"totalNum":80,"result1":"35","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"96-28=","type":"-","one":96,"two":28,"correctNum":72,"totalNum":81,"result1":"68","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"85-22=","type":"-","one":85,"two":22,"correctNum":73,"totalNum":82,"result1":"63","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"48+84=","type":"+","one":48,"two":84,"correctNum":74,"totalNum":83,"result1":"132","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"37-12=","type":"-","one":37,"two":12,"correctNum":75,"totalNum":84,"result1":"25","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"84-59=","type":"-","one":84,"two":59,"correctNum":76,"totalNum":85,"result1":"25","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"48-19=","type":"-","one":48,"two":19,"correctNum":77,"totalNum":86,"result1":"29","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"48-17=","type":"-","one":48,"two":17,"correctNum":78,"totalNum":87,"result1":"31","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"51-18=","type":"-","one":51,"two":18,"correctNum":79,"totalNum":88,"result1":"33","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"93-27=","type":"-","one":93,"two":27,"correctNum":80,"totalNum":89,"result1":"66","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"29+47=","type":"+","one":29,"two":47,"correctNum":81,"totalNum":90,"result1":"76","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"69-61=","type":"-","one":69,"two":61,"correctNum":82,"totalNum":91,"result1":"8","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"53-12=","type":"-","one":53,"two":12,"correctNum":83,"totalNum":92,"result1":"41","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"69-38=","type":"-","one":69,"two":38,"correctNum":84,"totalNum":93,"result1":"31","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"69-38=","type":"-","one":69,"two":38,"correctNum":84,"totalNum":93,"result1":"31","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"24-24=","type":"-","one":24,"two":24,"correctNum":86,"totalNum":95,"result1":"0","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"44-24=","type":"-","one":44,"two":24,"correctNum":87,"totalNum":96,"result1":"20","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"34+37=","type":"+","one":34,"two":37,"correctNum":88,"totalNum":97,"result1":"71","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"93-12=","type":"-","one":93,"two":12,"correctNum":89,"totalNum":98,"result1":"104","result2":"","correct":false},{"question":"93-15=","type":"-","one":93,"two":15,"correctNum":89,"totalNum":99,"result1":"118","result2":"","correct":false},{"question":"20-18=","type":"-","one":20,"two":18,"correctNum":89,"totalNum":100,"result1":"2","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"20-18=","type":"-","one":20,"two":18,"correctNum":89,"totalNum":100,"result1":"2","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"20-18=","type":"-","one":20,"two":18,"correctNum":89,"totalNum":100,"result1":"2","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"99-29=","type":"-","one":99,"two":29,"correctNum":92,"totalNum":103,"result1":"70","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"77-14=","type":"-","one":77,"two":14,"correctNum":93,"totalNum":104,"result1":"63","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"91-22=","type":"-","one":91,"two":22,"correctNum":94,"totalNum":105,"result1":"69","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"46-32=","type":"-","one":46,"two":32,"correctNum":95,"totalNum":106,"result1":"14","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"81-11=","type":"-","one":81,"two":11,"correctNum":96,"totalNum":107,"result1":"70","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"96-65=","type":"-","one":96,"two":65,"correctNum":97,"totalNum":108,"result1":"31","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"45-43=","type":"-","one":45,"two":43,"correctNum":98,"totalNum":109,"result1":"2","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"16-12=","type":"-","one":16,"two":12,"correctNum":99,"totalNum":110,"result1":"4","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"99-46=","type":"-","one":99,"two":46,"correctNum":100,"totalNum":111,"result1":"53","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"90-11=","type":"-","one":90,"two":11,"correctNum":101,"totalNum":112,"result1":"69","result2":"","correct":false},{"question":"41-24=","type":"-","one":41,"two":24,"correctNum":101,"totalNum":113,"result1":"17","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"96-26=","type":"-","one":96,"two":26,"correctNum":102,"totalNum":114,"result1":"70","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"90-66=","type":"-","one":90,"two":66,"correctNum":103,"totalNum":115,"result1":"24","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"92-62=","type":"-","one":92,"two":62,"correctNum":104,"totalNum":116,"result1":"30","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"100-16=","type":"-","one":100,"two":16,"correctNum":105,"totalNum":117,"result1":"84","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"99-22=","type":"-","one":99,"two":22,"correctNum":106,"totalNum":118,"result1":"77","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"82-15=","type":"-","one":82,"two":15,"correctNum":107,"totalNum":119,"result1":"67","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"56-19=","type":"-","one":56,"two":19,"correctNum":108,"totalNum":120,"result1":"37","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"91-58=","type":"-","one":91,"two":58,"correctNum":109,"totalNum":121,"result1":"33","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"33-24=","type":"-","one":33,"two":24,"correctNum":110,"totalNum":122,"result1":"9","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"82-37=","type":"-","one":82,"two":37,"correctNum":111,"totalNum":123,"result1":"45","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"66-42=","type":"-","one":66,"two":42,"correctNum":112,"totalNum":124,"result1":"24","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"97-11=","type":"-","one":97,"two":11,"correctNum":113,"totalNum":125,"result1":"86","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"54-45=","type":"-","one":54,"two":45,"correctNum":114,"totalNum":126,"result1":"9","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"89-19=","type":"-","one":89,"two":19,"correctNum":115,"totalNum":127,"result1":"70","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"37+96=","type":"+","one":37,"two":96,"correctNum":116,"totalNum":128,"result1":"133","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"69-26=","type":"-","one":69,"two":26,"correctNum":117,"totalNum":129,"result1":"42","result2":"","correct":false},{"question":"72-15=","type":"-","one":72,"two":15,"correctNum":117,"totalNum":130,"result1":"57","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"68-18=","type":"-","one":68,"two":18,"correctNum":118,"totalNum":131,"result1":"50","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"98-95=","type":"-","one":98,"two":95,"correctNum":119,"totalNum":132,"result1":"3","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"25-17=","type":"-","one":25,"two":17,"correctNum":120,"totalNum":133,"result1":"8","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"50-34=","type":"-","one":50,"two":34,"correctNum":121,"totalNum":134,"result1":"16","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"73-50=","type":"-","one":73,"two":50,"correctNum":122,"totalNum":135,"result1":"23","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"69-17=","type":"-","one":69,"two":17,"correctNum":123,"totalNum":136,"result1":"52","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"59-17=","type":"-","one":59,"two":17,"correctNum":124,"totalNum":137,"result1":"42","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"87-79=","type":"-","one":87,"two":79,"correctNum":125,"totalNum":138,"result1":"8","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"53-29=","type":"-","one":53,"two":29,"correctNum":126,"totalNum":139,"result1":"24","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"83-19=","type":"-","one":83,"two":19,"correctNum":127,"totalNum":140,"result1":"64","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"62+38=","type":"+","one":62,"two":38,"correctNum":128,"totalNum":141,"result1":"100","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"89-14=","type":"-","one":89,"two":14,"correctNum":129,"totalNum":142,"result1":"75","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"73-62=","type":"-","one":73,"two":62,"correctNum":130,"totalNum":143,"result1":"11","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"75-13=","type":"-","one":75,"two":13,"correctNum":131,"totalNum":144,"result1":"62","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"53-16=","type":"-","one":53,"two":16,"correctNum":132,"totalNum":145,"result1":"47","result2":"","correct":false},{"question":"65-17=","type":"-","one":65,"two":17,"correctNum":132,"totalNum":146,"result1":"48","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"90-33=","type":"-","one":90,"two":33,"correctNum":133,"totalNum":147,"result1":"57","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"60+15=","type":"+","one":60,"two":15,"correctNum":134,"totalNum":148,"result1":"75","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"53+45=","type":"+","one":53,"two":45,"correctNum":135,"totalNum":149,"result1":"98","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"91-69=","type":"-","one":91,"two":69,"correctNum":136,"totalNum":150,"result1":"22","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"96-72=","type":"-","one":96,"two":72,"correctNum":137,"totalNum":151,"result1":"19","result2":"","correct":false},{"question":"65-56=","type":"-","one":65,"two":56,"correctNum":137,"totalNum":152,"result1":"9","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"29+13=","type":"+","one":29,"two":13,"correctNum":138,"totalNum":153,"result1":"42","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"94-15=","type":"-","one":94,"two":15,"correctNum":139,"totalNum":154,"result1":"79","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"50-36=","type":"-","one":50,"two":36,"correctNum":140,"totalNum":155,"result1":"14","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"92-11=","type":"-","one":92,"two":11,"correctNum":141,"totalNum":156,"result1":"81","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"58-28=","type":"-","one":58,"two":28,"correctNum":142,"totalNum":157,"result1":"30","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"14-11=","type":"-","one":14,"two":11,"correctNum":143,"totalNum":158,"result1":"3","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"76-15=","type":"-","one":76,"two":15,"correctNum":144,"totalNum":159,"result1":"61","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"52-41=","type":"-","one":52,"two":41,"correctNum":145,"totalNum":160,"result1":"11","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"37-18=","type":"-","one":37,"two":18,"correctNum":146,"totalNum":161,"result1":"19","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"80-61=","type":"-","one":80,"two":61,"correctNum":147,"totalNum":162,"result1":"19","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"95-72=","type":"-","one":95,"two":72,"correctNum":148,"totalNum":163,"result1":"23","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"77-59=","type":"-","one":77,"two":59,"correctNum":149,"totalNum":164,"result1":"18","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"44-34=","type":"-","one":44,"two":34,"correctNum":150,"totalNum":165,"result1":"10","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"78-12=","type":"-","one":78,"two":12,"correctNum":151,"totalNum":166,"result1":"66","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"79-75=","type":"-","one":79,"two":75,"correctNum":152,"totalNum":167,"result1":"4","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"59-31=","type":"-","one":59,"two":31,"correctNum":153,"totalNum":168,"result1":"28","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"87-78=","type":"-","one":87,"two":78,"correctNum":154,"totalNum":169,"result1":"9","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"62-41=","type":"-","one":62,"two":41,"correctNum":155,"totalNum":170,"result1":"61","result2":"","correct":false},{"question":"77-46=","type":"-","one":77,"two":46,"correctNum":155,"totalNum":171,"result1":"31","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"82-55=","type":"-","one":82,"two":55,"correctNum":156,"totalNum":172,"result1":"27","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"40-14=","type":"-","one":40,"two":14,"correctNum":157,"totalNum":173,"result1":"26","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"24-18=","type":"-","one":24,"two":18,"correctNum":158,"totalNum":174,"result1":"6","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"72-54=","type":"-","one":72,"two":54,"correctNum":159,"totalNum":175,"result1":"8","result2":"","correct":false},{"question":"68-43=","type":"-","one":68,"two":43,"correctNum":159,"totalNum":176,"result1":"24","result2":"","correct":false},{"question":"14-12=","type":"-","one":14,"two":12,"correctNum":159,"totalNum":177,"result1":"2","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"12+84=","type":"+","one":12,"two":84,"correctNum":160,"totalNum":178,"result1":"96","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"58-13=","type":"-","one":58,"two":13,"correctNum":161,"totalNum":179,"result1":"45","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"77-16=","type":"-","one":77,"two":16,"correctNum":162,"totalNum":180,"result1":"61","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"66-14=","type":"-","one":66,"two":14,"correctNum":163,"totalNum":181,"result1":"52","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"96-16=","type":"-","one":96,"two":16,"correctNum":164,"totalNum":182,"result1":"80","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"83-23=","type":"-","one":83,"two":23,"correctNum":165,"totalNum":183,"result1":"60","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"68-11=","type":"-","one":68,"two":11,"correctNum":166,"totalNum":184,"result1":"57","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"57+89=","type":"+","one":57,"two":89,"correctNum":167,"totalNum":185,"result1":"146","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"97-34=","type":"-","one":97,"two":34,"correctNum":168,"totalNum":186,"result1":"93","result2":"","correct":false},{"question":"38-14=","type":"-","one":38,"two":14,"correctNum":168,"totalNum":187,"result1":"24","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"88-14=","type":"-","one":88,"two":14,"correctNum":169,"totalNum":188,"result1":"74","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"95-13=","type":"-","one":95,"two":13,"correctNum":170,"totalNum":189,"result1":"82","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"22+59=","type":"+","one":22,"two":59,"correctNum":171,"totalNum":190,"result1":"81","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"80-32=","type":"-","one":80,"two":32,"correctNum":172,"totalNum":191,"result1":"48","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"80-57=","type":"-","one":80,"two":57,"correctNum":173,"totalNum":192,"result1":"23","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"63-22=","type":"-","one":63,"two":22,"correctNum":174,"totalNum":193,"result1":"41","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"83-12=","type":"-","one":83,"two":12,"correctNum":175,"totalNum":194,"result1":"71","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"62-51=","type":"-","one":62,"two":51,"correctNum":176,"totalNum":195,"result1":"11","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"72-16=","type":"-","one":72,"two":16,"correctNum":177,"totalNum":196,"result1":"56","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"91-18=","type":"-","one":91,"two":18,"correctNum":178,"totalNum":197,"result1":"73","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"68-12=","type":"-","one":68,"two":12,"correctNum":179,"totalNum":198,"result1":"56","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"95-51=","type":"-","one":95,"two":51,"correctNum":180,"totalNum":199,"result1":"44","result2":"","correct":true}]